#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a full-stack software developer who enjoys working at the intersection of engineering and design. I specialize in building websites and apps that provide intuitive user interfaces while also being scalable and efficient. My goal is to make products that help people.

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Q&A** github.com/hczj/q-and-a

Virtual classroom with video chat, code/text editor, and whiteboard. Built in a 15-day sprint.

- ▶ Developed and implemented the features that use WebRTC and sockets.
- Led the architecture of database schema and database seeding.
- ▶ Live Demo: q-and-a-fullstack.herokuapp.com youtu.be/gxCZrut25-c
- Stack: WebRTC, Socket.io, React, Redux, Node, Express, Sequelize, CSS/Sass

# Finny's github.com/ekjc/grace-shopper

E-commerce website with filtering, shopping cart, and checkout. Built in a 10-day sprint.

- ▶ Implemented product catalog, admin functionality, form validation, and site design.
- People's Choice winner for best team project at Fullstack Academy.
- ▶ **Live Demo**: finnys-fullstack.herokuapp.com
- ▶ Stack: React, Redux, Node, Express, Sequelize, Mocha, Chai, CSS/Sass

## PubsPlus pubsplus.illinois.edu

E-commerce platform built for a client of Accuraty Solutions.

- Developed and shipped a customized website for the University of Illinois.
- Contributed all design and code as the solo developer assigned to the project.
- ▶ **Stack**: CSS/Sass, HTML, jQuery, C#, .NET, AngularJS

## PongPal github.com/chrismlusk/stackathon

Hackathon machine-learning experiment to teach an A.I. to play Pong in the browser.

- ▶ People's Choice winner for best individual project at Fullstack Academy.
- ▶ Live Demo: youtu.be/aaNyol\_B2rU
- ▶ **Stack**: JavaScript, TensorFlow.js, Python

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Teaching Fellow @ Fullstack Academy of Code

September 2018 to December 2018 — Chicago, IL

- ▶ Mentored and taught JavaScript concepts to 75+ bootcamp students.
- Oversaw four student projects as technical adviser and project manager.
- Conducted admission interviews for prospective students.

## Front End Developer @ Accuraty Solutions

October 2014 to December 2018 — Champaign, IL

- Developed and maintained code for client websites and applications.
- ▶ Tested sites to ensure cross-browser compatibility and mobile responsiveness.
- Customized content management systems (WordPress, ExpressionEngine, DNN).

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

**Front End**: JavaScript (ES6+), React, Redux, HTML, CSS/Sass, Bootstrap, jQuery **Back End**: Node, Express, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, RESTful APIs, GraphQL, PHP **Other**: WebRTC, Socket.io, Git, Web Accessibility, Mocha, Chai, Jest, Enzyme

### **EDUCATION**

# **Fullstack Academy of Code**

May 2018 to August 2018 - Chicago, IL

Software engineering bootcamp focused on front- and back-end JavaScript.

## **University of Oklahoma**

January 2009 to December 2012 - Norman, OK

▶ Bachelor's degree in journalism with a concentration in digital media.